My people died, and you have them talking about like it's a wonderful situation.
They make you feel guilty, and a lot of people don't get over that.
They just don't get over it.
I think they convince the people.
Do wealthy people leave, too, or not?
Places like Portland, are the wealthy people leaving?
People that can leave, are they leaving?
I think that they're moving to the areas that have been gentrified.
The Oregon governor, when she was saying, we don't need Trump here, she's walking around.
It's a very tight shot, if you notice that.
She said, Portland's just fine, you know, look at me, and they'll focus on the couple
areas of Portland that are very nice.
Well, she was saying that, and there were explosions in the background.
Yeah.
I mean, there was a reason they cropped it in.
We don't need this explosions in the background.
Anybody have anything else to say over here?